REX AMARILLO

Graphic Designer

Address Las Vegas, NV, 89123

Phone 702-487-2251

E-mail rexamarillo@gmail.com

WWW rexamarillo.wix.com/portfolio

A seasoned Graphic Artist and Designer, bringing 14 years of experience applying technical and creative abilities to diverse customer projects. Deadline-driven, focused on overseeing projects from concept through final delivery. Successfully creates brand messages, strategies, and key graphic productions.



Work History

Jul 2017 -Mar 2020

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

S&J CO. / Lionheart Ent Inc., One HitWonder, NV

- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Developed display, marketing and packaging materials to support product branding strategies.
- Created digital image files for use in digital and traditional printing methods.
- Applied knowledge of production to create high-quality images.
- Designed creative digital displays used in on-line advertising for local businesses.
- Efficiently handle high-volume workload, and ensure all deadlines are met.

Jun 2014 -Jul 2017

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Starbuzz LasVegas Inc., NV

- Develop artwork for social media, advertisement, and marketing materials.
- Create visually stunning concepts from scratch.
- Employed design fundamentals when selecting typography, composition, layout and color in design work.
- Built corporate brands by designing cohesive looks between elements such as logos and letterheads.
- Experienced with die-line construction, product label design, packaging design, and trade show booth design.

Jun 2008 -Jul 2013

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / APPAREL DESIGNER

Billionaire Mafia, LLC, NV

• Collaborate with team to design and develop full collection from scratch

under tight deadlines; in-depth knowledge in creating design tech-packs for production.

- Specialized in graphic T-shirt, denim, and trim designs.
- Design products for advertisement, and marketing materials.
- Develop company brand identity and marketing strategies.
- Created broad range of work using various design techniques.
- Researched trends and projected changes in Men's Fashion to capitalize on emerging opportunities.

Jan 2007 - GRAPHIC DESIGNER

JM Design Co, Salinas, CA

- Perform designs and illustrator job duties.
- Communicate effectively with colleagues, and clients to accomplish projects.
- Developed creative design for print materials, brochures, banners and signs.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection.

Mar 2007 - GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ZeroNyne Design & Screen Print, Morgan Hill, CA

- Execute critical color separations for screen-printing.
- Created new design from scratch, made appropriate changes, and arrangements to new design for best product outcome.
- Ability to take on challenge of designing for new variety of prints processes and materials.
- Met with customers to present mockups and collect information for adjustments.

Education

Sep 2007

Jun 2007

Jun 2005 - A.S. Degree: Graphic Design

Brooks College - Sunnyvale, CA

Skills

Website graphics

Digital imagery

Logo design

Image manipulation

Production layouts









Excellent





Mastery of Adobe Creative Suite

Advertising understanding

Trade show booth design

Excellent

Excellent

Excellent

Excellent

Excellent